[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1967 Roman Polanski film has been produced as a musical called  Dance of the Vampires.", "correct_answer": "The Fearless Vampire Killers", "incorrect_answers": ["Blood for Dracula", "Repulsion", "Blood and Roses"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What volcano located on the island of Tenerife represents the highest mountain on Spanish territories?", "correct_answer": "Teide", "incorrect_answers": ["Stromboli", "Santorini", "Duvalo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Spit can freeze in mid-air at the North Pole.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cats generally purr when they are happy, but they can also be heard purring in what other situation?", "correct_answer": "When they are distressed or in pain", "incorrect_answers": ["When they are hunting or playing", "When they are hungry or thirsty", "When they are lonely or angry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cerro Tololo Inter-American Observatory is a complex of astronomical telescopes and instruments, located on the territory of which country?", "correct_answer": "Chile", "incorrect_answers": ["Peru", "Spain", "Brazil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What important health benefit does cooked sweet corn provide?", "correct_answer": "It is rich in antioxidants.", "incorrect_answers": ["It contains more vitamin C.", "All of these", "It kills bacteria and viruses."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Sleepers, Father Robert Carillo revealed to Shakes that he, too, had spent time at the Wilkinson Home for boys.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Teenage heartthrob John Travolta played Billy Nolan in the 70s horror movie Carrie.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The ghost of Lady Jane Grey is known as The Nine Days Queen because of the violent ending of her life.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From whose novel was the motion picture Journey to the Center of the Earth adapted?", "correct_answer": "Jules Vernes", "incorrect_answers": ["Herbert George Wells", "Arthur Conan Doyles", "Selma Lagerlof s"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If we measure the acceleration due to gravity at the top of Mount Everest, it will be less than the acceleration at sea level.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about rodent species in general?", "correct_answer": "Rodents do not vomit.", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "The Latin word rodere, from which rodent originates, means rat.", "Rodents have canine teeth only on their lower jaw."]}]